KYLE WUELLNER

Shawnee, KS 66216

Phone: (913) 206-6963 | Email: kyle.m.wuellner@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/kyle-wuellner | Github: www.github.com/kwuellner | Portfolio: kwuellner.github.io

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer educated at the University of Kansas' coding bootcamp. Coming from a photography background strengths include HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Love using my creative side to develop a website that is not only pleasing but offers a good UX experience. Have experience working with teams to collaborate, problem solve and execute an idea, both professionally and academically. Looking forward to pulling from past work experience and education to develop new projects and websites with a team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX
- Node, Express
- MySQL, Mongo, Sequelize, MongDB
- JSon
- React

PROJECTS

Bamazon | github.com/kwuellner/bamazon

- A storefront shop that allows you to purchase items and track your inventory.
- I worked on all aspects of this program.
- Node.js and MySql

FreshAir | github.com/kwuellner/project2 | kwuellner.com/github.io/project2

- Travel website that builds a vacation around your response to survey questions
- Front-end development, UI, and some back-end authentication
- HTML, CSS

Liri Node App | github.com/kwuellner/liri-node-app

- App to search for concerts in town, songs on Spotify and movie information
- I worked on all aspects
- Node.js, Moment, Dotenv, Axios, multiple APIs

EXPERIENCE

Zimmer Biomet

Inventory Control Coordinator

December 2013-present Lenexa, KS

Assist in managing inventory for a multimillion dollar territory for multiple accounts like large hospitals, regional medical centers, and privately owned surgical centers. Monitoring supply and demand for trauma, extremities, sports medicine, and biologic products. Working with a team to process and oversee 500+ surgeries a month. Managing and forecasting the distribution of implants and instruments to ensure all surgeries are covered. Providing sales support for over 30 sales associates across Kansas and western Missouri.

Suture Express

November 2012-December 2013

Lenexa, KS

Scanning and packing suture products for hospitals and surgery centers located around the country. Visually inspecting all items to ensure none are damaged. Checking that all items are being shipped with the correct packing slip. Working efficiently and quickly to meet quotas for both units per hour picked and error free metrics. Restocking shelves with incoming product.

FedEx Ground

November 2011-December 2013 Shawnee, KS

Working in a fast paced environment pulling packages off a conveyor belt. Loading multiple trucks for local deliveries. Ensuring all packages are loaded in the correct location on the vehicle and in the proper order according to the drivers stops. Monitoring the belt so all packages are moving at an appropriate speed. Training new employees. Arriving early to make sure everything is ready before the shift starts.

Schmuhl Bros International

August 2011- October 2012 February 2010-December 2010 Kansas City, KS

Responsible for billing and inventory for all rail containers. Working with various rail yards to insure all containers are being sent to correct port. Daily contact with businesses for billing and information on order status. Managing products and inventory in the warehouse. Verifying trucks and containers are filled/loaded with the correct products. Accurate and detailed data entry in Excel.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: University of Kansas Overland Park, KS A 24-week full stack web developer program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.